stcltrk.com 2014-02-09

# VitruvianLeads - Innovative Online Advertising

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes how VitruvianLeads.com (VitruvianLeadsor "We") collects and uses the information collected through the website at VitruvianLeads.com (the "Site") and the related advertising services (the "Services") that we provide, which enable you to see targeted advertisements. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Site and Service. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. 

We do not collect any personally-identifiable information.Our Service collects your IP address, the domain name of each web page you visit, and the text content of the web pages you view. We do this so that you can receive targeted advertisements, which appear in a variety of forms including without limitation pop-ups, pop-unders, banner ads, cursor ads, image overlays, and search results. We do not use any of the information we collect to attempt to identify you personally. Our Serviceinteracts with your computer by: 1) obtaining your IP address so we can ascertain your general geographical location; 2) processing the domain name of each site you visit and the text content of each web page you view to determine the type of content of advertisements we enable you to see. Our Service communicates with your computer to cause advertisements to appear. After these ads are displayed, the information we collect and analyze is deleted. We do not share any of this information with other companies.

Our Service is made available to you as an element of 3rd party software that you installed onto your computer. Thus, to stop our collection and use of your information, simply uninstall the software using your computer's Control Panel to access the Add/Remove Programs function.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy. Any such modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. If any modification is unacceptable, your only recourse is not to use the Site.

This site is owned and operated by 

Digital Beacon, LLC  
10805 Rancho Bernardo Rd., suite 145   
San Diego, CA 92127

You may contact us at [biz@vitruvianleads.com](mailto:biz@vitruvianleads.com) .

Effective Date: September 16,2013
